{"easyQuestions":[{"questionText":"Family","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"חבר","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"זר","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"משפחה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"ילד","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Friendship","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"משפחה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אהבה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ידידות","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"קשר","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Computer","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"מסך","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מקלדת","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מחשב","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"מצלמה","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Weather","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"חום","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מזג אוויר","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"גשם","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"סערה","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Food","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"משקאות","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"פירות","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ירקות","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אוכל","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Happiness","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"עצב","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"רגשות","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אושר","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"פחד","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Nature","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"עיר","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"טבע","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"הר","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Music","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"ספורט","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"תרבות","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אוכל","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מוזיקה","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"School","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"בית","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"עבודה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"בית חולים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"בית ספר","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Book","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"עט","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"נייר","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"ספר","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"מחברת","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Pen","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"ספר","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"עט","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"נייר","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מחברת","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Love","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"שנאה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אמת","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אהבה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"כסף","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Work","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"בית","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"זמן","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"עבודה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"פנאי","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Dream","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"מציאות","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"יום","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"לילה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"חלום","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Travel","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"מסע","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מטוס","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"נסיעה","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"רכבת","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Time","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"מקום","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"זמן","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"כסף","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אוכל","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Money","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"זמן","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מקום","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אוכל","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"כסף","isCorrect":true}]},{"questionText":"Rain","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"שמש","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"רוח","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"גשם","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"חום","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"House","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"בית","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"דירה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"סוכה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"גג","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Tree","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"עץ","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"פרח","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"דשא","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"גן","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Shoes","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"נעליים","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"חולצה","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מכנסיים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"חצאית","isCorrect":false}]},{"questionText":"Car","answerOptions":[{"answerText":"אופניים","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"אופנוע","isCorrect":false},{"answerText":"מכונית","isCorrect":true},{"answerText":"מטוס","isCorrect":false}]}]}